♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ way down in deep 13 ♪
♪ dr. Forrester
and tv's frank ♪
♪ were hatching
an evil scheme ♪
♪ they hired a temp
by the name of mike ♪
♪ just a regular joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ so they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ and they shot him into space ♪
Get me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can find
la-la-la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and we'll monitor his mind
la-la-la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
mike can't control ♪
♪ where the movies begin or end
la-la-la ♪
♪ he'll try
to keep his sanity ♪
♪ with the help
of his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
- Cambot!
- Show yourself!
- Gypsy!
- I'm not ready!
- Tom servo!
- Hello there!
- Crow!
- That's one "o"!
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts
la-la-la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself,
"it's just a show ♪
♪ "I should
really just relax ♪
♪ for mystery science
theater 3000!" ♪
- Okay, you guys ready?
- Yes.
♪ Oh, the yellow rose
of texas ♪
Hi, everyone. Welcome to
the satellite of love.
I'm mike, this is tom servo,
and this is crow t. Robot.
And we're just working on
one of those
beloved old standards.
You know, these are
the kind of songs
- everyone can enjoy--
- hey, hey, hey, mike!
There's something coming in
on the hexfield.
- Huh?
- Whoa.
- Hello? Yes?
- Yeah, hello, arnie.
Uh, arnie?
Arnie, you sound weird.
Look, you gotta get over here
and sign these papers.
I know you're not thrilled
to hear from me.
Uh, ma'am, I think
you may have the wrong number.
There's no arnie here.
Wow. That was weird.
Well, let's go.
♪ Oh, the yellow rose
of texas ♪
Mike, the hexfield again.
Look, I know arnie's there.
You don't gotta
cover for him, chopper.
Chopper, this is you, right?
Look, you don't have to cover
for him,
he just has to get over here
and sign these papers.
- Lady, uh--
- hold on. What?
- What's for supper?
- Eggs.
- Again?
- Yes, again!
So, is arnie staying there
with you, chopper?
Uh, this may take a while.
We'll be right back.
Look, chop, do not let him
take advantage of you.
He's a sweet guy,
but he takes, takes, takes.
Mommy's on the phone!
♪♪
Of course, I was only about 16
when me and arnie got hooked up.
Man, he was so good looking...
Back then.
Nowadays, it's just
his whiskey breath,
this dump, and 4:00am calls
from the police.
Oh, hold on,
my bacon's on fire.
Now. Now!
Wow.
Well, you know, she did have
a certain je ne sais quoi
about her, didn't she?
No.
Let's see
what benny and june are doing.
Hello, murray, automata.
Say, what's one of
the most popular
forms of exercise
this month? Hmm?
Hmm? Well, that's right.
The recumbent bike.
As I see it,
recumbent creators were afraid
to make them
too comfortable.
Well, I'm not afraid. Ta-da!
The recomfy bike!
[Chuckles]
Doctor f., could you tuck me in
before my ride?
Of course, franklin.
There you go.
Check out the reading lamp,
night-stand,
and goose-down comforter.
Of course, we may have to ditch
the wheels and the pedals
to make room for the ice machine
and espresso bar, but--
uh, doctor,
I can't get it to go.
Well, try harder, you load.
But there's kind of
a lot of stuff here.
"There's kind of
a lot of stuff here."
Nappy time,
don't you think, frank?
Back up to you, margo.
[Snoring]
Well, that is really,
really useless.
[Laughter]
Anyway, our invention
pumps new life
into that age old deck
of playing cards.
Let's face it,
with only 52 cards,
there's only so much
you can do.
A jack, queen, king,
give me a break!
Aah, that's why we each came up
with our own new cards.
To sort of
spice things up a bit.
Mine is the eight
of chris lemmon.
Son of the very talented
jack lemmon.
Chris lemmon?
Yeah, I just loved him
in duet.
Huh, well, my card is todd.
Just todd.
Todd is helpful.
And todd is there for you.
- Todd? Todd?
- Yeah.
Well, is he--
what value is he?
Is he royalty or what?
Well, todd doesn't like
to be pigeonholed.
He says the term "royalty"
puts limitations
on your dreams.
Well, okay, what happens
if I lay down an eight
of chris lemmons?
Who wins?
Ah, no. Todd says, in america,
values are meaningless.
And he doesn't
like competition.
Actually, now that
you bring it up,
todd says your chris lemmon
card has issues
he needs to work through.
Well, if it's okay with todd,
why doesn't crow go next?
- What do you got, buddy?
- Oh, yes, yes!
My card is the...
[Trumpet sound]
Crow of diamonds!
Woo! Crow of diamonds.
Crow, I think you missed
the whole point
of this exercise.
Well, todd thinks it's okay.
Todd...
[Snoring]
[Laughs]
Enough of your
touchy-feely crap, nelson.
Today's movie
really gets going
about two minutes
before the closing credits.
It's another
bert I. Gordon pain parade
called
the beginning of the end.
And I hope you have
health insurance.
[Giggles]
On your life!
And then later on,
todd's gonna show me
this really great
massage technique,
and photos from his weekend
with robert fulghum, and--
[buzzer sounds]
Ah, movie siren, dog gone it.
Oh, we got a movie siren.
Come on, movie siren!
Hey, you know, I've got
a good place for todd.
- Yee!
- Oh, that's fine.
- Boy, you're fickle.
- I'll deal with it.
Looks like this is where
ichabod crane takes his dates.
Ooh, and you know, it'd be sexy
until you think,
"it might be my parents!
Oh, my god!"
No!
♪ Ask me why ♪
Hey, how does he sing
while he's kissing her?
♪ Never be afraid ♪
You taste like vinyl.
Bet you anything
there's gonna be a claw
hanging from
their door handle.
Ooh, no, not there.
Yeah, that's it. Oh, yeah. Oh.
[Screams]
Don't give me a hickey!
What-- what?
Huh. Oh. What?
The beginning
of the end already?
- I don't...
- It just started!
And the june taylor dancers!
Is this a flashback
to previous credits?
I wonder what that lady saw
when she screamed there.
Lou ferrigno?
Maybe.
Oh, stop it.
I'm getting nauseated.
- Maybe she saw bigfoot.
- Bigfoot pizza?
- No, I... maybe.
- I don't...
Oh, could I get some dramamine
for this credit sequence?
- You okay, buddy?
- Yeah, I think so.
Please welcome your new richmond
high-school marching band.
- Honey.
- Mike, I think I need a bucket.
[Vomiting]
Credit sick, there.
Hang in there.
Ah, I'm okay.
Put your head
between your knees.
Okay.
- Don't slip in it.
- Does that feel better?
- Yeah.
- Now.
- Wow.
- Ugh.
So this is like
beginning of the end
bold, condensed font
here, huh?
Oh, no.
[Vomiting]
Honey, do you think
you could keep down
some 7-up and soda crackers?
- Uh, no.
- Some luke warm pork?
[Vomiting]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
One more time!
[Humming theme]
There's too many notes.
So is something going to happen?
I don't know.
- Huh?
- [Michael] Hums.
Folks, we'll start the movie
as soon as our ride
gets here.
Man, that car radio
is loud, huh?
You know, bird eye sure doesn't
skimp on the opening.
This is 2-5-4
on the ludlow swing--
and we're hopelessly lost.
We'll be checking-in
in 45 minutes.
[Dispatcher]
10-4, car 2-5-4.
Klp 6-4-6.
You want to say hi
to headquarters?
Pull over.
I saw something.
If they had to pull over
every time you see something,
it's going to be a long ride.
Rantoul is only
five miles away.
Yesterday,
it was 10 miles away!
Someone's moving the sign.
- Whoa!
- Something happened
off screen here.
Uh, ms. Mansfield?
I'll report in.
You know, these things just
don't do anything to me
emotionally anymore.
I'm drained.
Hi. Me again.
Car 2-5-4 to champagne urbana.
[Dispatcher]
Urbana to 2-5-4, go ahead.
Car 2-5-4 to urbana,
we're investigating an accident
at junction 45
and ludlow cutoff.
- Foul play suspected.
- No duh.
Uh, hold on,
I'm gonna read you a poem.
Oh yeah, the driver may
have been william summerfield.
177 decatur street,
ludlow, illinois.
Oink bada-boom.
[Dispatcher]
One of you stay on the scene,
the other investigate
the ludlow address. 10-4.
Car 2-5-4.
Klp 6-4-6.
Man, he's good.
Whelp, this is it, I guess.
I don't know what to say, carl.
I'll never forget you.
- But--
- no, just go.
Looks like a girl's sweater.
The car was attacked
by a sweater!
So why is walter winchell
in this scene?
Hey, it's my size!
[Dispatcher]
Come in car 88.
Uh, excuse me. That's for me.
I'm the man.
♪ Angels of the morning ♪
♪♪ [servo hums]
- YELLO!
- CAR 88 TO CHAMPAIGN, URBANA.
McKENNIZE HERE, GO AHEAD.
[Dispatcher]
Car 2-5-4 has failed to report.
Is that car in your area?
- I beg your pardon!
- No, not here.
10-4 car 88.
This is klp 6-4-6 urbana,
calling car 2-5-4,
come in car 2-5-4.
McKENNZIE? McKENNZIE!
YOU'RE BREAKING EVERY RULE
IN THE BOOK!
Urbana to car 2-5-4,
come in car 2-5-4.
Uh, houston we got a problem.
[Dispatcher]
Urbana to car 2-5-4,
come in car 2-5-4.
[Footsteps approach]
I was the first one here!
- Hello, I'm at ludlow!
- It's really dark!
- The whole town's destroyed!
- It's really neat.
- Everybody's gone!
- I'm lonely.
You got to do something.
You won't believe this.
Send help!
Lots of help, quick!
Oh, forget it.
Executive producer
steven bochco.
Yeah, basically I run
the army, yep.
How you guys doing over there?
I don't feel very fun today.
Come on. Just come on.
The director's brother-in-law,
ladies and gentlemen.
What the-- hey!
You know, bird eye did this all
in one take.
- Amazing.
- ♪♪ [michael hums]
You know, when I was a boy
we didn't have fast movies.
Sometimes we had to wait
three or four hours
for something to happen.
I love that story.
Anyone need to go
to the bathroom, go now!
[Servo]
♪ how will you make it
on your own? ♪
She's got a radio tuned
to the marching band station.
All sousa, all the time.
Hmm. Must get vivarin.
[Servo snores]
Now, this is an improv
that really went nowhere.
[Servo and crow laugh]
Okay, men, private reese
is feeling vulnerable today.
It's up to us to cheer him up.
Your hover buick
will get you there in style.
Hover buick.
Servicemen, great.
[Crow mimics tires screeching]
All right, lady,
just follow the arrows.
- Any chance
of getting through?
- Nope.
What happened?
Look, lady, just detour.
Will you, please?
Don't make me pull you
from your car
and beat you
with my nightstick.
Mmm, quiet.
Smooth ride.
Oh, now they're
gonna have to turn
the rear projection screen
around, too.
Guys, this is so not illinois.
[Crow giggles]
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Mmm. I wonder what they're
doing here. Well--
gee, martial law is fun.
♪♪ [Servo vocalizes]
Whoa,
that is a texas style camera.
Tell him to take
that detail out of there.
The old man is sending
a replacement.
That's my line!
Finally remembered.
I'm sorry, soldier,
I should've explained.
I'm audrey aims,
national wire service.
- Yes, ma'am.
- How do I get there?
Sorry, my orders are
to let no one through.
Well, that surely doesn't
include the press.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
But no one--
good job today, lance.
Carry on.
Well, was it very bad?
- So ashamed.
- Many get hurt?
Look, lady, you're not going
to fish any information
out of me.
Now, why don't you get back
on the main road?
It's a about mile south.
Hear that, guys?
I really told her off.
Mile south, ha!
He likes me.
I think we're dating.
Oh, I locked
my keys in the car-- oh!
Hey! The car started
without her even doing anything.
[All mimic
marching band music]
Jimmy jam does his thing.
- [Dispatcher]
Until further notice--
- I'm paul frees.
A traffic will continue
to be routed around
the ludlow area
according to special orders--
- good morning.
- I'm turning myself in.
I'd like to see
your commanding officer.
Here's a little something
for you.
Well, I'm sorry
but the colonel's busy.
Too busy for these?
Perhaps captain barton
can help you.
"I am deaf.
Please give me money." Hm.
- Send her in.
- Ma'am.
File on dalton trumbo, sir.
Thanks, lieutenant.
Sit down, please.
Now, get up again.
[Chuckles]
Aren't you the audrey aimes
who covered korea
for that picture magazine?
- That's right.
- Well, I hated it.
I read the book you wrote
after the war.
Liked it very much.
Why, thank you.
You're with national wire
service now.
I was on my way
to chanute field
to do a picture story
on a new jet plane
they're unveiling,
and I ran into a road block.
- So?
- Yeah, you're right.
What was I thinking about?
There was a town
beyond that road block,
a town that isn't there
anymore.
Until we find out
exactly what happened,
we'd like to avoid publicity.
Do you have any idea
what happened?
I'm sorry, miss aimes.
Maybe after
this whole cover-up,
we can have coffee sometime?
You can't suppress
a story like this.
We're not trying to,
miss aimes,
but until we have
more facts...
♪ This is the army,
audrey aimes ♪
Will you give us your word you
won't release a story
until we give the go-ahead?
You have my word.
God, your hair
smells wonderful.
Sometime during the night,
the town of ludlow
was completely demolished.
- And?
- Town's population,
about a hundred and fifty
people, vanished.
Vanished?
No bodies, nothing.
It was
some david copperfield stunt.
There must be some trace.
I know it's hard to believe,
miss aimes...
But I'm koko taylor.
We've a special detail going
through the wreckage
for two solid hours
and couldn't find a thing.
Two solid hours?
We don't know.
On account of the fact
we're not very smart.
150 people just don't vanish
into thin air.
We're still trying to find out
what happened,
if you'd like to sit in.
Yes, thank you.
I would.
I've got a clarinet in my car.
Hey...
[Imitating arnold ziffel's
from green acres]
Dave, what time did you leave
ludlow last night?
Must've been after 11:00.
Arnold ziffel's father.
My son-in-law was watching
the television news at 10:30,
so I sat down
and watched that.
Then I caught letterman.
And my daughter wanted me
to sit there and talk a while.
Then I got to thinking
that I had to get up early.
- Your point, please?
- So I had to go.
- Did you notice anything
strange...
- Hoiman!
...about the house or about
the way the family acted?
Other than wanting my son-in-law
to diaper me, nope.
- When you're driving
out of town...
- Hm, nice likeness.
Nothing out of way
in the street, the building,
or the sky?
No unusual light,
some sound or movement?
Objection, your hon-- oh.
Well, I heard something
sound like thunder.
Couldn't see it so good
'cause of the rain.
...a plane went over.
You are so high.
All right, dave.
I can call you again
if I need you?
- Oh, yes, yes.
- You know you can call me dad.
My next guest, rose marie!
[Imitates cheering]
The telephone company's
official transcripts?
It was a mistake.
I didn't mean to--
the last call from ludlow
at 11:59 p.m.
When did you first notice
anything wrong with
the ludlow connection?
- Andrew jackson?
- Old hickory.
I phoned the company linesman
to go out there right away.
So the telephone lines
could've gone down
anywhere between
11:59 and 4:45.
Yes, yes,
is that what you want?
All right, thanks.
You've been very helpful.
Man, she's a tough old bird.
[Whistles]
Okay, bye.
Oh, colonel sturgeon,
miss aimes,
national wire service.
How do you do?
Audrey aimes?
I've read a lot of your stuff,
seen a lot
of your photographs.
Reading your cleavage now.
- Yello!
- Yes?
[Man on phone]
Set to go sir,
whenever you're ready.
I'll be right there.
All right, I've got to pick up
phil at play practice.
I hope you understand
our problem,
our need to keep this quiet.
Yes, captain's briefed me.
Then he pantsed me.
If anyone wants me,
I can be reached
in ludlow by radio.
How's chances
of me going along?
- Not this trip.
Maybe later.
- Maybe later?
In any case, not until we
know what's out there.
Oh, by the way, colonel,
my camera was taken from me
at the road block,
by one of your men.
I'll give orders
to have it released.
I'll take the long way
out of here.
Bert I. Gordon film after all.
See ya.
What a loser.
There has to be a logical
explanation for this.
A town of 150 people
just doesn't disappear.
This one did.
Yes, but in general
they don't disappear.
That's my point.
Hey, now she's on
the abbott and costello
show set.
Oh, man,
I should've taken home ec
or gone into teaching
or nursing like
all the other girls.
Gosh, I'm 21
and I'm still not married.
Yello!
[Woman on phone]
Chicago mobile service
operator.
I'd like to place
a person-to-person call,
please,
to mr. Norman taggart.
- Me being
one of the persons of course.
- ...National wire service.
The number
is murray hill 4, 4836.
- Man, I miss those kind
of phone numbers.
- New york.
[Imitating frank nelson]
Eeeeyeeessss?
Lined up that jet plane story
already?
I'm not on the jet story.
Norm, listen.
I'm onto something
I think can be real big.
Me.
Oh, he's right handed.
Where?
Scribble, scribble.
Scribble, scribble
as though I'm writing something.
What do you mean
we can't print it?
I've given my word
to hold off for a while.
- Now, listen, norm.
- You're fired.
A plane flew over ludlow
last night about midnight,
just about the time
the lid blew off.
Check on it.
And check washington.
See if they had an atomic
installation in the ludlow area.
Okay.
Who am I, your stringer?
Call me back as soon as you
have anything, right?
Good-bye.
- Jeez, her guy friday.
- Cool.
♪♪ [Humming]
Hey, we found the 150 people.
You were right.
Sorry, miss, you can't--
oh, it's you again.
I know I can't
but I'd like to have my camera
back, please.
Colonel sturgeon said he was
going to speak to somebody.
Hey, corporal, mathias,
she wants her camera back.
[Phone rings]
I'll get it.
It's probably for me.
Yello.
Oh, do you know our jackpot
today?
What's the score?
Wrong track, baby.
The airlines confirm
a commercial liner
over ludlow
at 12:03 last night.
And there are no
atomic installations,
secret or otherwise,
within 75 miles of ludlow.
Well, it was a possibility.
The only
who've been playing around
with radioactive materials
in your vicinity
is the u.s. department
of agriculture.
- Anything there?
- Department of agriculture?
Yeah, they've got
an experimental project,
just outside paxton.
U.s. department
of agriculture,
illinois experimental station.
Okay, I've got that.
I'll keep in touch.
I've gotta go.
I've got someone in my office.
♪♪ [Humming]
I have a city idea-- chicago.
I think it might work.
[Chuckles]
Let's get out of here.
♪♪ [Whistles]
- [Whistles]
- Wow, I don't know about
this movie, you guys.
Nothing's happening.
I think maybe we should call
the mads.
We can do that, right?
Well, I guess,
but I wouldn't advise it.
Yeah, I mean, why get them
involved?
I mean, I just think
we should call the mads.
Why don't we call the mads?
- No.
♪ My baby takes
the morning train ♪
♪ she works till 9:00-- ♪
Frank? I could not stop picking
at that pan of lemon bars.
I ate half the pan.
You're so lucky you could eat
anything and not worry.
Oh, pshaw, I'd give anything
to have that complexion
of yours.
Oh, frank.
Hey, wow, v.I.C.I. Is on.
You know, frank,
this is exactly what
I wanted to do today,
just have the whole day
to ourselves.
I'm declaring this
national our day.
[Laughs]
Please, do not let me eat
all of this.
Well, I shouldn't.
Oh, my god, frank.
Switch on a game.
[Cheering,
coach whistle on tv]
[Grunting]
So, I guess we can call
the mads, huh?
- Yeah.
But you know what?
I don't think I'm going to do
that for a while.
No, I don't think so.
We'll be right back.
Stranger fellers.
Come on in.
Just working on plutonium.
Herman badillo.
I'm looking
for the farnstein wedding.
Tomatoes like brahms.
Wow, suddenly salad.
Excuse me.
Man, those are cherry tomatoes.
I beg your pardon.
I never promised you
a rose garden.
Hey, this is the produce
department, isn't it?
I beg your pardon.
We're working overtime
to keep dom deluise fed.
The more he ignores me,
the more I'm attracted to him.
Oh!
- Hello.
- I'm peter graves.
Hello.
I spoke to him, but I guess
he didn't hear me.
Oh, he's a deaf mute.
You insensitive little...
Working with radiation
can be dangerous.
I smelled that.
An accident last year
cost him his speech
and his hearing.
And 600 bucks.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm looking
for the project director.
I'm the project director.
My name's ed wainwright.
What can I do for you?
Oh, excuse me a minute.
Kind of a vague sign language.
I'm sorry, frank.
Oh, we dropped
his chocolate sampler.
Nothing to worry about.
Just a slight catastrophe.
You have these catastrophes
very often?
Well, as often as we have
government cover-ups.
All the time.
It's hard to keep these things
from getting in.
These are snails.
Last summer
it was caterpillars,
and after that it was
grasshoppers by the drove.
This guy eats anything.
And just last week
it was beetles.
Now it's bagel dogs.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Wainwright,
I'm audrey aimes.
I'm with national
wire service.
I suppose you heard about
what happened in ludlow.
- Yes.
- I'd like to kiss you
full on the mouth.
I'm trying to find out
what was responsible,
and it occurred to me
that radiation of some sort
might've caused
the destruction out there.
No, I don't think so.
Here.
Let me show you
a giant crouton
we're working on.
We're the only people
around here using
radioactive materials.
Maybe I shouldn't be keeping
my lunch in here.
I don't know.
And isotopes aren't explosive.
And they're packed
with vitamins.
I'm afraid your answer
isn't here.
Oh, I see.
The big brush off.
Tell me, is this thing
really a strawberry?
Yes, and these are tomatoes.
And those are turkey franks.
This we hope is the future
of the american farmer.
And for that matter,
all farmers everywhere.
- Can you eat them?
- No, not yet.
I don't even like tomatoes.
We hope to developed
one day a hybrid
that can be eaten.
How is it there hasn't been
any publicity on this?
Oh, there have been a few
stories in farm journals,
but to most of the public,
these giants
are just freaks of nature.
No practical value.
- Get this thing off me.
- How did they get so big?
Radiation
causes photosynthesis,
that is the growing process,
to continue night and day.
Radio isotopes act as
a sort of artificial sun.
That's it, real her in, boss.
Fascinating.
Tell me, what's he doing?
Well, that's plant food,
essential minerals.
And he's eating it.
Keeps the plants
from burning themselves up.
They have to be fed
constantly.
Actually the fruit
would grow much larger
if we didn't limit
the stimulation.
Speaking of stimulation.
Maybe you'd like to do
a story on us.
I'd be glad to tell you
more about the work.
Ooh, schmooze overdrive.
Thank you very much.
I'd be very interested,
but right now I'm working
on this ludlow story.
If you could see my hands right
now, you'd be horrified.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
Don't start.
♪ That's my mother dear ♪
♪ she helps me through
everything I do ♪
Three jerks and a jill.
Colonel.
You here?
They wouldn't let me inside,
so--
colonel, springfield
is on the line.
Colonel, you just got back
from ludlow.
You said, after you got back,
I could go.
- I said maybe.
- Well, how about it?
Nothing will be open
to the press.
Oh, colonel, be fair.
I played ball with you.
Give me the jump on the other
reporters that'll be in here.
At least let me take
some pictures in ludlow.
I promise I won't put them
on the wire until tomorrow.
Well, I guess
you rate that.
For effort anyway.
Bratton, take miss aims
to ludlow.
Yes, sir.
And I hope you have
a strong stomach.
Gabe kaplan's performing.
He's nice.
We're going to take
some pictures in ludlow.
If we're not back
in 15 minutes,
better come in after us.
- Yes, sir. Let 'em through.
- Look at that guy over there.
He's taken a few in the head.
That wouldn't stop a kid
on a big wheel.
Toughest job you'll ever love.
All right, captain.
Way to go. Whoo!
Huh? Suddenly it's turned
into topper.
Somebody turn down
the albert glasser music!
I can't concentrate!
I wish the larsons would take
better care of their yard.
- Oh, it's a disgrace.
- Oh, look at that.
My goodness.
Wanna stop and loot?
Hey, it's a star city.
Look. There's
a perfectly good 2 x 4.
This was no boating accident.
♪♪ [Humming]
I've had enough.
I can't stand reality.
- Whoa-ho, colonel.
- Some use calendars
to tell age.
I could use ruins
to count mine.
Oh, am I here, too?
I was 25 when I went through
seoul after the shells.
I'm wearing panties right now.
I was 20 when I took my camera
into cologne and berlin
after world war ii.
24 when I saw dylan
at the bitter end.
Must be used to it by now.
Captain, there's some things
you never get used to.
Like underarm odor.
Thanks.
How about my kiss?
How about a drink
to wipe away some memories?
Good way to get rid
of the jitters.
I know a little place--
how do a hundred
and fifty people vanish
into thin air?
Yeah, terrible.
Martinis?
Around this part of the country,
things seem to have
a way of vanishing.
Only a couple of months ago
it was a warehouse.
Kind of fell apart over night,
just like ludlow.
Good-bye, captain.
Wha-- hello?
Okay, okay,
you can have your raise.
Hey, he saw
and heard something.
Women on the verge
of an atomic breakdown.
She wants me so bad.
Let's get on
with the harassment
so we can get some work done.
Hi. Did you decide to come
back and do a story on us?
No, as a matter of fact,
I came back for some help.
I'd like you to do me a favor.
- Oh, yes.
- Anything I can.
Does it involve taking
my pants off?
Remember the warehouse
that was destroyed
about three months ago?
I want you to take me
to see it.
Then to dinner and a movie.
Oh, I'd like to,
but I've got too much work
on my hands right now.
How about tomorrow?
Three months ago a warehouse
was destroyed,
and one person in it vanished.
This morning ludlow
was destroyed.
All the people in it vanished.
Coincidence? Read the book.
Don't you see
a possible tie up?
Look, lay off. Lay off!
It's possible, I suppose.
What do you want me to do?
Just ride out there with me
and take a look at it.
I don't understand
what good that'll do.
The authorities
investigated it thoroughly.
Look, I'm coming on to you.
Don't you get it?
The sheriff thinks in terms
of crime and publicity.
You're a scientist.
You think in terms
of cause and effect.
Maybe you'll see something
that the sheriff missed.
That shouldn't be
too difficult.
Still, i-- I don't know.
Hm?
Frank, that's filthy.
I should wash
your hands out with soap.
What's he saying?
He says that your lips
are easy to read,
that your theory makes you
a very bright girl in his book,
and he'd like to go along
with us.
And he's being held here
against his will.
Eh-- oops.
- Peter, no!
- Oh, no! God!
When you barge
into people's lives
and drag them off to places
they don't really want to go,
aren't you sort of in danger
of becoming unpopular?
Slug bug.
Ow.
Oh, I though you...
How'd you pick
such an occupation?
Wait, this isn't a stick shift.
I guess I was just born
inquisitive.
Ever since I can remember,
I wanted to know
the why and wherefore
of just about
everything I saw.
I inherited my knack
for the camera from dad.
Your dad, as a matter of fact.
My curiosity supplied
the nose for news,
and the camera supplied
the memory.
So there you have it.
What about you?
Have you always been
interested in science?
Well, after
my german dancehall days...
I guess I always have been
one way or another.
I used to fool around
with radios
and anything electrical
when I was a kid.
I was a radar officer
during the war,
and then I went into this
when I got out.
Look. Let's just play
the radio for a while. Hm?
Oh, yes, I remember now,
that every time I read
one of your articles,
it was datelined from some area
of flood or famine or war.
Made me realize
what a sheltered life
we scientists really lead.
- What do you think of that?
Huh?
- Sheltered?
Look what happened to frank.
Yeah, watch this.
Hey, frank!
[Laughs]
Geez, frank, you should've
thought about that
before we left.
Doesn't look that great,
but they got great
union rings here.
Huh? What?
- What the?
Hey, this is even worse
than that other stuff
that we didn't know
what it was.
Well, it's a fixer upper.
That's for sure.
Looks to me as though
some force
had to push these walls out
from the inside.
Think it was an explosion?
It couldn't have been.
Any explosion big enough
to destroy this warehouse
could certainly
have been heard in ludlow.
At least we saved this hat.
What was it that they kept
stored here?
Wheat.
Almost a million bushels.
That's a lot of wheat.
It was surplus
to keep the market
from being oversupplied.
- I hate wheat.
- Doesn't it strike you
as a little strange
that out of all that wheat
there's not
a grain left anywhere?
No, that's nature's way,
audrey.
Birds probably cleaned up
the leavings.
He's not deaf.
They're talking
about wheat over here.
That's frank's way of yelling.
Wha-what?
Wow, that's
a whole lot of skirt.
I see what you mean, frank.
What is it?
What-what did he say?
You see how barren
this ground is?
I don't know.
I've seen horses leave it
like this.
This is deeper than horses go
and much more thorough.
And much more fun.
Practically down to the roots.
Now, horses pick and choose.
They leave patches.
I was in fury,
so I know that.
This is barren.
Please don't say that word.
I'm very sensitive right now.
Leave it to old frank.
He'll make a botanist
out of me yet.
You're head
of a government lab,
and you need lessons
in botany?
Well, just lay off.
I try to teach him
what I can
about my field of study.
He tries to teach me
what he can about his.
Aren't you a botanist?
No. No, I'm an entomologist--
the study of insects.
Oh, fascinating.
How come you're working
with plants?
God, you're right.
Well, the existence
and development of plants
and insects
are very closely related.
They're highly dependent
on one another.
As a plain matter of fact,
one couldn't live
without the other.
- Mm-hm.
- Bogus.
That's why I can't understand.
Ground like this is usually
teeming with insects.
This area's completely
devoid of it.
Hm, you like fiddle faddle?
I think I'd like to get
some shots of this.
I'm going back to the car
for my camera.
I'd really like to see you rub
your forearms together.
Hey, an indian head penny.
- Here, let me help you.
- [Chirping]
[Grunts]
What was that?
- [Chirping gets louder]
- I don't know.
It might be coming
from behind that rather large
grasshopper.
I think.
Luckily the grasshopper's
closed captioned.
Frank, would you quit clowning
with that giant grasshopper?
Oh, no, stop!
He's signing "aah!"
Oh, no.
You can't save him.
Get in the car.
Quickly, get a really big
applesauce jar
with holes poked in the lid.
Hey, diane arbus,
why don't you take a picture?
You've got a camera.
We'll send help.
B-B-Bye.
So feel like chinese?
The geiger counters
show no radioactivity
to speak of, sir.
Only background.
There's got to be
an explanation somewhere.
I've got your explanation
for you, tom.
- We've got bugs.
- Now, listen.
You've known me ever
since I came to paxton.
You know I'm not given
to hysteria,
and you've got to listen
to me with an open mind.
[Whimpering gibberish]
What are you talking about?
I'm talking
about giant locusts.
Giant locusts are responsible
for all of this.
I love it.
No evidence of any explosion,
colonel.
The buildings look
more like they were hit
with a battering ram.
We found these guns
at the scene,
the kind people keep
in their home.
They've been fired.
- Can I go home now?
- Okay. Lieutenant.
Now, listen, tom.
These are eight feet tall,
some even bigger.
They're vicious,
merciless killers.
Now, ed.
Stops them cold
with that "now, ed" every time.
Lieutenant, telephone
springfield again.
Tell them I'm still waiting
for those specialists.
- Yes, sir.
- Frank johnson is dead.
He was killed
not half an hour ago.
It was horrible.
Obviously you're both
under strain--
why won't you listen?
You've got to get
some soldiers out there
before more people
are killed.
Miss aimes, the governor asked
me to exercise digression
in dealing with you.
Please don't make it any harder
for me than it is.
You have to believe us.
Listen, you've seen the giant
plants out at the lab.
Are you trying to tell me
you bred these things?
Yep, then I deep fry them.
In a sense I did, yes.
Hey, it's ike.
Say hi to ike, everyone.
- The locusts must've gotten
into the lab.
- Hi, ike.
- I like ike.
And they ate some
of the plants
or some of the radioactive
plant food.
Their cell division
accelerated immediately.
That is they started
to grow abnormally fast.
So it's your fault.
They have
a constant food supply
to sustain this growth.
So a couple of months ago
they wandered into the grain
elevator outside of town.
When they grew
to this giant size,
they pushed their way out.
Oh, they just pushed
the building down.
- Yes.
- Okay, okay, forget locusts.
Giant panda bears
and they fly.
One of them has the strength
of 10 men.
There are probably
2 or 300 of them.
So last night, not satisfied
with eating the grain,
they came to ludlow.
- Yes.
- [Chuckles]
Even if I went for your story
about the size,
it'd be hard to believe
they'd attack people.
- Sergeant.
- Have these people killed.
That report come in
from the chemists?
No, not yet, sir.
Why won't you listen?
I am listening.
We saw frank johnson killed
by a giant locust.
Sure, and there are
reliable people
who've also seen
flying saucers
and weird little men
from mars.
Take another look
at that town out there.
Or have you found the answer?
God, I want pork right now.
Lieutenant.
Yes, sir.
I'm taking a detail out
for a look around.
You're to keep radio contact.
I want 10 men.
- Get them on the truck.
- Yes, sir.
- All right, ed?
- Strap this on.
You can show me the exact spot
where you saw
well, whatever it was you saw.
No.
Well, after all,
it's his grasshopper.
These ribbings are so much less
gentle than pleats.
It's a good thing they're not
huge eyebrow mites.
The joads are armed
to the teeth.
"Californee."
♪ We're not afraid
of big old bugs ♪
♪ army guys like gentle hugs ♪
That too windy back there
for you guys?
Is the truck
just going to dump them?
Is this a snipe hunt?
[Imitating beeping]
- All right.
- All right!
All right, all right.
[Grunting]
Big piles of potatoes.
Defending countries...
Men, we're gonna get us
some crazy grasshoppers.
Why didn't they give us nets
instead of rifles?
Mm-hm.
Observational humor.
All right, men.
Pair out.
That's one of my favorite
mountains in illinois
back there.
Hey, somebody strung out
nice roofing material here.
Here's the spot, tom.
He wet 'em here.
Where's the body?
There isn't any body.
I don't think I've implied
there would be a body.
There isn't any body.
All right, men,
into the woods.
I don't know, crow,
it's probably just me,
but the whole idea
of a screenplay
based around the life
of peter graves
just spells box-office poison.
And then to go and narrow
the focus so much.
Here, let me sizzle it
for you, mike.
Peter graves went to the
university of minnesota, right?
- I guess.
- "I guess" nothing.
The man went to the u of m,
and that's exactly
what my screenplay exploits.
Well, can we just get on
with this, please?
Yes.
[Clears throat]
Here we go.
Just plain peter.
The u of m years.
Or peter graves goes
to college
at the university
of minnesota.
A screenplay
by crow t. Robot.
Okay, okay, let's go.
I'm only doing this because I
need the stage time, pin beak.
Okay, servo.
Okay, okay.
Act i-- peter graves enrolls
at the university of minnesota.
- Okay, okay, here we go.
- ♪♪ [humming]
Hi, I'm the registrar.
May I help you?
Yes, I'm peter graves,
and I'd like to enroll
at the university of minnesota.
That's-- that's it.
Act ii.
Mike, you've got to help me
with the character
because I don't have...
Thank you.
Act ii-- peter graves
attends his first class.
Hi, I'm peter graves.
Is this biology 101?
- Yes.
- Good.
I'm peter graves,
and I'm in the right class.
Huh. Um, act iii.
Act iii-- peter graves
enjoys dorm life.
Okay. Think fast.
Aha, I'm peter graves,
and I'm enjoying
some good natured ribbing
with one of my many new pals
here at the university
of minnesota.
Act iv-- extracurricular
activities.
Oh, this is great, this one.
I'm peter graves,
and I was wondering
if you could direct me
to the natatorium,
as I'm attending a swim meet.
It's that way.
Thank you.
I'm peter graves.
Okay. Uh, act v--
peter finds his calling.
I'm peter graves,
and I'm beginning
to take an interest
in the theater arts
and speech communications
here at the university of--
- crow, how many acts are there?
- What?
Uh, 15.
- Uh, crow?
- Yeah.
Not criticizing here,
but were you worried
about the redundancy factor
or not or...?
Well, I felt my point was
important enough to risk that,
but let's do the climax.
I think you'll really like it.
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's get to the climax.
All the cards over now.
Act 15, graduation.
I'm peter graves.
Thank you for the opportunity
of learning
at this fine institution.
As I look back,
I remember fondly
my enrollment process
where, had you been there,
you might've heard me say,
"hi, I'm peter graves,
and I'd like to enroll at
the university of minnesota"
or the time when i--
that's it!
Crow, you are way out there!
- Hey.
- Way out!
Gee, uh, oh...
I gotta agree with him, crow.
No, but, mike,
no matter what you or servo
may think of my little
screenplay,
if it's convinced
just one person out there
that peter graves went
to the university of minnesota,
then I've done my job.
- [Alarm buzzing]
- I'm peter graves,
and we've got movie sign
on a&e.
[Gasps, mutters]
- Oh.
- That's enough.
All right.
♪♪ [Humming]
- Hey, frank.
- How was that brothel
last night?
Maybe we can train
one of these giant crickets
to pull a plow, huh?
Everything's not a joke, ted.
- I don't like this thing.
- Oh, take it easy.
Maybe they were big ants.
Didn't see them real good,
did you?
Grasshoppers are good eating.
Yeah? Mustard or ketchup?
Shouldn't they all be
different ethnic types?
No. No kidding.
Ate them once down in mexico.
You better watch your step.
They liable to get even.
We're having a lighthearted
conversation
in the midst
of unbearable tension.
Well, at least it's a nice day
to be out, eh?
You must've seen something.
Mr. Wainwright's a scientist.
He's trained to see things
right.
These days they blame
the atom for everything.
Bad health, bad crops,
bad weather.
- Bad lieutenant.
- Now it's grasshoppers.
They couldn't have just dreamed
up this guy frank
being knocked off.
- Ah.
- [Mocking] Ah.
Now, were your glasses
in the case,
or did they just drop
out of your pocket?
- [Chirping]
- Oh! Oh, mr. Kot-tare!
What would mitchell do right
now, huh?
Gladys, quit bugging
the stevens!
It's bernard herrmann music
out there.
They sense I'm peter graves.
They're all too embarrassed
to admit they hear anything.
Hey, is this
what we're looking for?
- Huh?
- Yow.
Sit. Stay.
[Screaming]
Just get a giant screen door!
Hey, let's pull one leg off
and watch it try to walk.
I think we should've waited
for the sanctions
to take effect.
You see, if you're going
to have a war,
you should wait first.
[Imitating gun fire]
Just run
in that general direction.
We're going to get
a lot of raid, right?
We're going to get a whole lot
of rain, right?
Exterminate
with extreme prejudice.
Oh, this is a bug hunt, man.
♪ When you wish upon a star ♪
Sometimes you can't hear the
pincer with your name on it.
Hey, you guys know
where we can get some decent
weed around here?
Better get the place ready.
Yeah.
America responds to the new
robert urich/faye dunaway
sitcom!
Al bundy takes command!
Can I get a ride
with you guys?
Help yourself to a gun, peter.
♪ John jacob
jingleheimer schmidt ♪
Oh, my god!
Insects trained
by russ weatherwax.
One weekend a month, my ass!
Well, that went well.
And every available man.
I'm throwing a party.
Also get some air support.
We'll bomb them
out of that forest.
Yeah, that ought to hold
the little...
What are you going to do?
Going in there and wipe out
every last one.
- They'll slaughter you.
- Not this time.
Dig this.
I want light auxiliary
brought up with company h.
You don't have enough men.
There will be three regiments
out there tomorrow by 03:00.
You don't understand.
You still don't have enough men.
Not enough men for
a couple hundred locusts?
There are more
than a couple hundred.
- But you said before--
- that was before I heard them
screech.
The noise they make convinces
me there are more.
How many are there?
I don't know.
There could be countless
numbers.
I think you better call
in the regular army, tom.
Where would I get off calling
the regular army
to handle some oversized
grasshoppers?
Boys, boys, don't fight.
Why, they'd section eight me
right out of the service.
[Phone rings]
Lieutenant, take charge
of the east sector.
[Grunts]
Hi, anyone for nutter-butters?
Excuse me.
Bum leg.
I'm afraid he doesn't
understand how serious this is.
After all, he knows what
the military is capable of.
Oh, just jump on me, too.
He has faith in regimental
fire power
because he's seen it work.
♪ Faith, faith, faith, baby-- ♪
He's never come up with
anything like this before.
You've done all you can.
No, no, I haven't.
In a way I feel responsible.
In a way?
He's in deadly danger
if those locusts break out
of the forest.
Well, back to the salt mine.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to washington.
Maybe the army people
will listen to me.
I'll go with you.
Maybe I can help.
I saw them, too.
- All right.
- Mind if I catch a ride?
We've got to convince them,
audrey.
We may be witnessing
the beginning of an era
that'll mean the complete
annihilation of man.
- Hm.
- Annihilation?
- What will I wear?
- Annihilation.
The beginning of the end.
Uh, real good, then.
Bye-bye.
And guests of
the beginning of the end
stayed at
the beautiful capital dome.
Inferior guests
stay at the defense department
annex.
This, gentlemen, is the enemy.
Moving pictures.
This locust, more commonly
known as the grasshopper,
is almost identical
to the giant locusts of ludlow
except for its size
and the fact that the giants'
wings failed to develop.
They cannot fly.
Now I'll get comfortable.
The locust is intelligent
but strong.
He is armed.
- Locusts follow a leader.
- His name's larry.
Like the bee and the ant,
they're able to communicate
with each other.
- Aunt bee?
- This communication, or call,
is produced by the hind legs.
Let me demonstrate.
This is the 1956 australian
locust plague.
And this is the 1910
fruitgum company.
- Covering an area
of 400 square miles.
- Seen it.
- We've been plagued by locusts
since biblical times.
- You're not funny.
- There are various forms
of combating them.
- Sit down.
As a matter of fact,
in our own country,
the early settlers of the
massachusetts bay colony...
- Armed themselves
with bundles of brush...
- Ow, ow, ow...
And drove millions of locusts
into the sea.
Today, despite the fact
that we've developed powerful
insecticides...
I haven't got a series.
...the locust
still inflicts damages
to the tune of $25 million
in the united states alone--
california, colorado, texas.
Uh, connecticut.
- Even this small locust
will attack a man.
- Little bastard.
It has two powerful jaws
with a ridge full
of sharp teeth.
And they're vicious gossips.
And they'll kill other insects
and devour them.
If no other insects
are available,
it becomes a cannibal,
turning on its own kind.
She wants me.
What in the good god
are you talking about?
Now, you've seen
what the locusts can do
in its normal size,
smaller than your thumb.
Imagine, if you will,
a locust that's grown
bigger than a man
and is continuing to grow,
some larger than others,
but each one a deadly killer.
I think it'll go
something like this.
I hope you realize
we haven't much time.
You are a scientist,
mr. Wainwright.
You know what locusts can do.
- I'm a soldier.
I know what guns can do.
- Together we could...
I feel secure the illinois
national guard
can handle this situation.
Just like they handled
the chicago convention.
You want to say something,
general hanson?
- No, sir.
- I'm deeply ashamed.
I was greatly impressed
with your presentation,
wainwright.
I'm sure all of us were.
Thank you very much
for coming.
Go in peace and say no more.
I'm afraid my presentation
didn't impress you
quite enough, general.
I don't understand you.
I mean, that when
the locusts start to move
out of that forest,
I'm not sure you'll be able
to stop them.
What are you suggesting we do,
mr. Wainwright?
Hit them with everything
you've got now.
You need more men,
a lot more men.
You need tanks
and heavy artillery.
As of now the full strength
of the illinois national guard
is in the line, surrounding
the ludlow national forest.
Go away now.
As I said before,
mr. Wainwright,
you are a scientist.
Why not leave the fighting
to the military?
Did you just call me a wussy?
Well, guess I'll just leave you
a few of my brochures.
No, that's fine.
Thank you.
Urgent call from paxton,
illinois, sir.
Here, you talk in this end,
sir.
- General short here.
- General shorthair?
I don't know, stuffing.
Whatever you make.
[Muffled]
Help us, general...
Help, please.
You will fly to paxton
with mr. Wainwright.
You'll take charge
of operations.
Hey, I'm vindicated.
How many dead?
Wainwright,
I owe you an apology.
The locusts have broken
through our defense line.
Thousands of casualties.
Our troops are reorganizing
to prevent paxton itself
from being overrun.
I'm trying not to laugh, sir.
♪♪ [Humming
raiders of the lost ark theme]
The hill position
in the suburbs of paxton
must be held.
Otherwise the 100 miles
between paxton and chicago
will lie open.
Can I get some nuts?
[Man on intercom]
General, we can't land in
paxton, sir.
Why not?
It just came over the radio,
sir.
Giant locusts have overrun
paxton at 1400.
[Muffled]
I told you so.
Head for chicago.
Yes, sir.
Well, no more lunches
at milda's cafe, huh?
"Dear abby, I'm an elderly
woman who doesn't enjoy se--"
oh, this came
to the wrong place.
Captain,
I want these positions held,
and I want them held
at all costs,
if humanly possible.
Captain, have your map people
immediately turn out over
300 overlays
showing
the chicago defense line...
Yes?
Thank you,
sergeant whisper thin.
Yes, nothing gets tobacco juice
out of your clothes.
Boy, I read slow.
Major everett...
Our road trip to peoria
has been cancelled.
- How about squadron 12?
- They haven't reported in yet,
general.
Let me know
the moment you hear.
Yes, sir.
- I'll be with you in a moment.
- Okay, son.
Bill, you'll proceed at once
to temporary ghq central sector
and assume command.
- ROBERT FROST.
- YOU WILL ORDER THE 81st
ARMORED DIVISION
to proceed without delay
to fort sheridan in chicago.
Have the cg report to me
upon arrival.
And get this man an arm.
...the defense department to
alert the following divisions--
THE FIRST ARMORED,
THE 40th, THE FIRST AIRBORNE,
THE 92nd AND THE 76th.
Okay, any salad with that?
Uh, what's your problem?
At the rate refuges are pouring
into chicago, general,
our emergency staff
won't last long.
Then we'll feed them crickets.
Yeah. That's it.
Ech, now, why did I do that?
Toxaphene is one
we haven't tried.
How good is it?
Almost as powerful
as chlordane.
With no after taste.
All right, ship 2,000 gallons
out to the base.
- Take a pint for yourself.
- Excuse me.
[Phone rings]
- Hello.
- Bat lab.
Speaking.
Squadron 12 just reported.
They say they came down
in the day
and practically drowned
the enemy in insecticide.
I just got a haircut,
and it hurts.
The chlordane didn't even
slow them down.
They threw it back at me
and laughed.
We'll have to come up
with something stronger.
I'll do my best, general.
Good-bye.
How about chlordane
with a tiny drop of retsin?
It's no good.
Forget it.
Doesn't cause
enough birth defects.
What else
can I do around here?
Make myself useful.
Ah, here we go.
Oh, no, new petitions
against tax again?
Dear god.
Looks pretty bad, doesn't it?
No, you look fine.
Thought you went back
to new york?
Well, the big story is here.
Look, your editor called
you back because it was
too dangerous.
I wanted to be here.
Nothing we've done so far--
insecticides, fire bombs,
nothing has done any good.
And so little time.
Well, you're doing
everything you can.
Everybody is,
but it's not good enough.
Maybe if I try to toss
a quarter into that thing.
In time the beasts
will inherit the earth.
There's your answer!
A fine pilsner!
Lee marvin in the bridges
of madison county.
♪♪ [Humming]
Hey, general, where you going?
I'm going to decatur!
I'm gonna shoot that
paper-hanging son of a bitch!
[Death rattles]
Sorry about that. Sorry.
Well, I guess wait till the
grasshoppers show up, huh?
All quiet
in the western suburbs.
There's no sign of the locusts
yet, general.
Out.
Should we just continue
firing at random?
The jack benny program.
And with the lock
of five divisions
to the western south...
Mr. Mitchell.
General hanson is confident
that he can keep the menace
at bay.
That's dennis the menace.
The air force and marines
are moving into position.
To back up those forces
already deployed by the army.
The one advantage our forces
hold over the enemy...
Don't sit so close, dear.
...always reveal
their intention to attack.
Which is nice.
Before every attack,
the locusts send forth
this warning
in the form
of a high-pitched screech.
Looks like the sun king's bell
on top of their tv
until it reaches
ear shattering proportions.
Sounds like mariah carey.
The screech reaches
its full intensity
when the locusts attack.
Copy.
We've got every available man
on the line, major,
and I think there's no question
but what will be.
- [Chirping]
- Hush now.
Oh, I love a spring rain.
I shouldn't have worn
my butt dress.
Oh, great, they're early.
[Clamoring]
The cubs don't win the pennant!
Meanwhile,
at the boy scout jamboree
at pottawattomie park...
I wanna drive your tank.
I call the front.
Oh, so far seems pretty--
oh, my god, look out!
Hold your fire, men.
We'll negotiate!
Cricket lighter.
Just $1.49.
- Wow.
- Oh, I'm hit.
They got jiminy!
Get 'em!
We were pinned
down near elgin.
Aurora was pretty bad.
Bad, it stunk in there.
Whoo, sweat lodge.
Okay, okay. Okay, gotcha!
Whoops. Oh, I'm sorry.
Let me clear the shot.
This is where you step back
and say, thank god
for my exoskeleton.
[Muffled]
This is flying officer
jim cavanaugh.
The dan ryan's covered with
tobacco juice.
You might want to try an
alternate route.
Let's all welcome bob hope,
ladies and gentlemen.
Even out best footage
can't stop them!
Have you seen
my mommy and daddy?
[Crying]
Damn nazi grasshoppers.
Hi, I'm going to sneak
in here to say,
"hope you're enjoying
the show.
Bye for now."
Ho, I've got a great gun.
No, I don't need a bazooka.
The orkin army will storm
the beaches of lake forest.
We're going to have to get
organized.
We should not be losing
to grasshoppers, people.
So is this protecting chicago
at all costs, sir?
They keep coming, general.
They're lobbing aphids at us!
They're hammering at a single
point in our line.
I don't know how,
but they've arranged air cover
from the mexican army.
They cut off our supply lines
and ate the radio men.
No grasshoppers were hurt
in the making of this film,
huh?
I don't believe it!
They're using hannibal's
surprise!
They keep coming, general.
They're moving closer.
Still they come,
wave after wave.
They've broken our code,
and the sergeant
was a grasshopper under cover.
[Mumbling]
...Coming.
They're pouring through
a breach in our lines.
We're being cut off!
Oh.
We interrupt this program
for an important announcement.
Aah!
...have reached
the chicago south side
and nearby suburbs.
I repeat. The giant locusts
the chicago south side
and nearby suburbs.
They control
the cement business.
Take shelter in basements.
Take shelter in...
Do not dress line grain.
Do not panic.
Love grain.
Attention, please.
Keep moving.
Do not block the highway.
Do not covet
thy neighbor's manservant.
Stamp all fires dead out.
Do not panic.
Oh, my god.
Oh, jeez.
Oh, yah.
Hey, hey, I want
a chicago-style hotdog.
In grant park,
on lake shore drive.
♪♪ [Hums theme
to the bob newhart show]
Uh, excuse me, am I on 24?
Yeah, come on, baby.
Comb that hair.
Boy, I wish I was a tub
of dippity-do.
Yes, yes.
This is a single room.
Ah, you women take so long
to get ready.
I'm kidding.
I didn't say
the skirt was ugly.
- General.
- Ed, miss aimes.
Grab a chair and sit down.
They've got a picture
of russ bender.
I sent for you because
of a new development
it may be favorable to us.
Bruce geller called.
The locusts had stopped
their advance.
They're huddled
in the alleys and buildings
just outside the loop.
The locusts get cold.
When the temperature
drops below 68 degrees.
They just stop moving.
Maybe now's the time we can
move in and destroy them.
They aren't in hibernation,
sir.
They'll move
if they're provoked,
and they're just as deadly
as ever.
Just shoot me down.
When the sun comes out
tomorrow,
they'll be active again.
The air force is standing by
with a b52 loaded
with an atom bomb.
Oh, good,
maybe they'll get larger.
You can't drop an atom bomb
on chicago.
Sure you can.
Washington has given me
authority to do just that,
as a last contingency.
If the bomb is dropped
early tomorrow,
there will be no loss of life.
The city will be evacuated
by then.
What about the property?
There will be a billion dollars
worth of damage
and a site that's too
contaminated to rebuild on.
- I realize that.
- I just don't care.
But if we don't drop the bomb,
chicago will almost certainly
fall.
Look, we'll move the loop
to schaumburg.
We'll drop at dawn.
If we don't come up
with something by then,
I'll make a final check
with washington
and relay their okay.
No chicago?
But why not?
Isn't there a chance the locusts
could die in the night
of the cold?
No, not at this time of year.
Anyway, they got blankets.
Takes 24 hours of exposure
at 14 degrees.
Is that cold? 14?
Isn't there some way you could
drive them into the lake.
In washington, you said
the settlers did that.
- [General] Settlers.
- Hm?
Oh, yeah, people who settle.
He early settlers
in massachusetts
did literally drive them
into the sea,
- but they weren't dealing
with giants.
- [Radio whistling]
Oh, that's my darjeeling.
Wait a minute.
We can't drive them.
- We can invite them to leave.
- Not drive.
We could attract them.
Attract.
I'll dress like
a sexy grasshopper.
Reproduce their call, general.
It might work.
It just might work.
A call for insects?
Call for insects.
Have you ever been duck hunting,
general?
A duck call.
Yes, there's one for bees, too.
They use it in apiaries.
- Bee call?
- It might work.
What do you need?
A tennis ball, an accordion,
and a picture of don ameche.
I need an audio oscillator.
I need an audio-- two--
two audio oscillators.
Three-three-four.
Make it four.
I need an oscilloscope.
I need some high-frequency
radio equipment.
And a boat, a fast boat.
Whatever you need, we'll get.
Oh, then a bottle
of johnnie walker blue.
There's something
I have to get myself,
something that'll tell me
when I've succeeded.
What's that?
I live giant grasshopper.
Get out.
I'm not with him.
Here, live giant grasshopper.
[Whistles]
Here, live giant
grasshopper boy.
All right, drop your segmented
thorax and come out.
We've got your blade of grass
surrounded.
♪ I sing whenever
I sing whenever I sing ♪
♪♪ [humming]
Sir, please.
Savages. Worse than british
soccer fans.
They've got to be
around here somewhere.
Hey, hey, hey,
they're stealing the truck!
- Hey!
- So long, suckers.
All right, men.
Off the truck.
Ow. Ow.
Major, I suggest that you send
some of them that way
and some down there,
and you and I try the alley.
Brilliant!
Now, you four men go that way.
You men that way.
Just go out anywhere.
You know what to do.
What is this, a welcome respite
from all the action?
You know, major,
lately I've been watching
the unfolding of me.
And yet I can't love.
I appreciate that.
Yet I don't think
it's appropriate right now.
So, doc, how's the science game
working out for you?
I thought about getting
into science.
I got a c in it
in junior high.
Actually it was interior design
always thrilled me.
That was my knack for a while.
Textures and--
they just set off
the grasshopper alarm.
♪ The night chicago died ♪
♪♪ [humming]
Shut up.
- [Can rattles]
- [Imitates machine gun]
Oh, sorry.
So if they scissor me in half
with their powerful jaws,
please don't keep me alive.
Science and the military
working side by side.
That's where the grasshoppers
go to smoke.
Finally the men's room.
I've been looking for that.
I know what you're thinking,
grasshopper.
Did I fire six shots or...
[Grunts]
Oh.
I wasn't scared.
Were you scared?
[Chirping]
It's that damn kid
on the pogo stick again.
Let's get him.
Louis, I think this is going
to be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
I'm peter graves.
Hey. You know,
giant grasshoppers--
you just take it for granted
you can find them,
and then when you want them,
they disappear.
Yes, I jerk.
Oh, god, leave me alone.
You know, chicago
is a 24-hour town.
Yep.
Trumpy.
Hey.
[Blowing whistle]
The von trapps have escaped!
Come on! We got one in here!
Come on!
And keep quiet.
We just got him down.
Meanwhile, in castle wrigley.
You're dead, graves.
I've got friends.
This is a dead man
I'm looking at.
Well, it looks like you were
having a pretty good time
for yourself
out in peoria last night,
eh, hoppy?
It's lucky we got
one of the smaller guys.
This'll go easy on your if you
just give us some names.
Not too close, major.
We put that cage up
in a hurry,
and I don't know
how strong it is.
How about some grass
in here?
A month ago I was teaching my
engineering class at university.
It was safe and secure.
But look at me now.
I'm not safe and secure.
Now I'm 37 years old,
and all of a sudden I realize
for the first time
how much I've taken life
for granted.
Not now.
I guess that's something you
can't take for granted, major.
Ed, how will you know when
you've got the right sound?
- I have no idea.
- He'll tell us.
- How?
- He'll react to it.
And this polygraph
will record his reaction.
How long will it take?
It's a matter
of trial and error.
Could take 10 minutes
or 10 hours.
I think pete
was affected by that gas.
- Yeah.
- We don't have 10 hours.
We've got theater tickets.
They're dropping
that bomb at dawn.
I hate to ask you this,
but where are your nipples?
How does this work?
Well, I've just attached these
wires from the polygraph
to the two copper strips
at the base of the cage.
Now, the locust,
like every other living thing,
has galvanic reflexes.
Come here, just closer.
Come on.
...in direct ratio with activity
or emotional stimulation.
Next time, flat foot,
you're mine.
I don't understand.
In other words,
when we hit
the correct sound or signal,
the grasshopper
will react to it,
and the polygraph
will record the change.
Mm-hm. Hm.
You notice how steady
and regular the movement
of the needle is now?
Oh, yes.
When we reproduce
the grasshopper's call,
the lines will become longer
and highly irregular.
Like a lie detector test.
Sit down.
This is the first time
a grasshopper ever got one.
Now, if you'll keep your eye
on the needle
for any unusual jumps...
We'll just head off.
Got a little surprise
for you guys.
- Goody.
- This is going to be
really fun.
Will you set up
that big brick wall?
- [Laughing]
- Okay, mr. Tom servo,
are you ready for this?
Oh, you bet, mike.
This movie's given me
a great idea
for a stand-up routine.
Now, take your seat.
Get ready.
Okay, lights, cambot.
Thank you,
thank you, everybody.
What a beautiful crowd tonight,
huh?
Say, did you ever notice
the difference between
grasshoppers and locusts?
Well, for one thing,
locusts have shorter antennae
than grasshoppers.
Grasshopper's walking
down the street like,
"hey, look at me.
I've got some big antennae."
Where a locust is walking down
the street, it's more like,
"oh, no, my antennae
are so small."
Smaller antennae, you see,
on the loc--
have you checked out
the ovipositor
in a female grasshopper?
You see, they use them
to drill holes in the grass.
You know what I mean?
They're like,
"oh, I need to drill a hole.
Hope I brought my ovipositor."
But female locusts
have a short ovipositor,
so they're more like,
"oh, no, my ovipositors
are so small."
What else can I tell you
about myself?
Oh, long-horned grasshoppers--
are they something or what?
You know, they come
from the family tettigoniidae.
Am I right?
Ladies, back me up on this one.
Now, you see, locusts,
they're different
from the tettigoniidae,
especially those
rocky mountain locusts.
They're known
as melanoplus spretus.
Thank you.
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
Tip your waitresses.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Well, tom, that--
that really, really--
sucked. Sucked.
No, it was very good.
It was informative, too.
Gee, thanks.
I was thinking of doing it on
the tonight show.
Oh, tom, you were good,
but you've got to be
really, really good
to be on the tonight show.
How about david letterman,
then?
They don't just let anybody
on letterman.
How about chevy chase?
Hey, there you go.
Send him a tape.
I think you've got
a real shot at it.
- We'll be right back.
- Thank you.
Very good.
Very byron allen.
So are you in love
with me yet?
I have my rights.
Well, I've just come to see
what you've done
with all the grant money.
Oh, my god!
Wainwright,
you've had your chance.
Now it's the air force's turn.
God, the stress
and the bomb...
Hello.
Operator. Operator,
this is a top-priority call.
Get me general wagner
at the air base.
You hear me, graves?
You're not getting
anything out of me.
Nothing.
[Muffled]
One moment.
♪♪ [Imitating muzak]
I'm getting
the pina colada song.
Look, general,
the locusts outside
will stay put
until the temperature reaches
68 degrees.
That's about an hour
and a half from now.
Oh, this phone
is smooth, sleek--
hello.
Wagner, corridor's
been evacuated.
Unless you receive instructions
to the contrary,
by 06:16, that is...
Oh, call it 8:00.
- That's 90 minutes from now...
- That good for you?
...you will order
your b52 crew
to deliver the bomb
on the designated target.
Start with the shedd aquarium.
Repeat the instructions
back to me.
Yes, I love you, too.
Correct.
Will you stop questioning
the grasshopper?
There's no time to fool
with that now.
Major, get a detail of men up
here to move this stuff.
He's got an hourglass shape.
Bring some extra grenades.
There's some in my staff car.
There's a new lab set up
for you
at my new hq
outside the city.
I can't move now.
You can't stay here,
not with an atom bomb
hanging over your head.
Don't have any choice.
I'm peter graves.
Up till now we've been using
a filtered signal,
and it hasn't worked,
but it's just possible
that the hearing apparatus
of the locust
can detect
harmonic frequencies
above the human range.
To test these frequencies,
I need every minute
that's left.
If you'll just give me one man
to replace miss aimes.
I'm staying.
Look, this is no time to be
worrying about a big story.
I'm not worried about a story.
Look, I just wanna drop
my a bombs.
Will you please leave
before it's too late?
No.
Major, you and a detail
of two men
will remain here
with mr. Wainwright.
I will station men
at three observation posts--
one in the suburbs,
one near the art institute,
and one on top
of the downtown hotel.
One on top of me.
Also a helicopter
will spot from above.
There will be a getaway car
parked downstairs
at the main entrance.
I suggest you use it by...
08:00, I guess.
By 5:45 at the very latest.
If you are successful,
contact me at once
so I can stop the bomb.
Just a little bowl of wheat,
please.
It's 05, um...
[Imitating radio announcer]
Well, good morning.
You've got the loop here.
It's going to be
a nice day today.
We're going to get bombed.
You probably heard about that.
They're scraping
the grills at the billy goat
this very moment.
Mm.
I'm a broke grasshopper.
That's all I am, honest.
[Whirring]
Sounds like "sweet lorraine."
Do I really have to stay here
for this?
So where's the razzmatazz?
I don't see it.
Hm. Nope.
Gino's?
I've got to have
those glengarry leads.
Have you ever associated
with crickets?
Have you ever taken part
in a plague?
Have you eaten grass
in excess of $1 million?
Damn tandy equipment.
Folks, as for traffic today,
there's none.
Can't explain it.
Whatta ya know?
Boy, the convention business
just went straight down hill,
didn't it?
Wow.
Look at that.
[Whirring]
What the sam hill is he doing?
I'm not going to admit
my failure.
It's shaping up to be
a pretty nice day.
Maybe go get some christmas
shopping done.
Not a lot of competition.
[Whirring continues]
It's a long
kathleen battle aria.
Maybe he's innocent.
Maybe they got
the wrong hopper.
Doh, I forgot to turn
this thing on.
[Imitates whirring]
Ed, look at this.
He's got high blood pressure.
I think you've got it.
This is what it sounds like
when grasshoppers cry.
By george, higgins,
I think we've got it.
[Miss aimes screams]
Whoa. Hm.
Oh, no, not the face.
You took out
a couple thousand eyes.
Pete! Pete!
Short, controlled bursts!
Hey, I've got it.
We could just shoot them.
Oh, well, acceptable losses.
I had to shoot him.
Well, let's chocolate dip
that grasshopper.
And get that thing out of here.
Bug fell and hit his head
against the bars
if anyone asks, right?
Back at it.
I want to polygraph
the doorknob now.
Emergency lab to chicago ghq.
Come in, general.
Are you there?
Now, listen to me, wainwright.
We found it, general.
We found the frequency.
Good. Now stand by.
I've got to stop that a bomb.
I'll get right back to you.
Chicago ghq to double b.
They're not going to let us
drop the bomb.
Don't answer it.
This is double b.
Come in, chicago ghq.
Over.
Hanson here.
Your mission is cancelled.
- Real sorry, boys.
- Return to your base.
Repeat the message.
Over.
It's the commies.
Mission cancelled.
Return to base.
- Over.
- Repeat it again.
Chicago ghq to emergency lab.
Right here.
The show is yours, wainwright.
All right, get that equipment
on the lake in a boat,
and I'll be your pied piper.
Get me my little green shoes
with the curly toes.
Oh, I love men who use
fairytale imagery.
♪♪ [HUMS
McHALE'S NAVY THEME]
He just polygraphed a sandwich.
He needs real help.
I still don't understand.
Why didn't you put
the oscillator in the boat
in the first place
to send out the call?
Why track them here?
Because we'd
never get them all.
Here, look.
Dilbert's a scream today.
Here we are
in downtown chicago,
near the lake.
And the locusts are scattered
all through the suburbs
and on the south side.
We'll send out the call
from here.
Yes, but that's going
to attract them to us,
not into the water.
- Shut up.
- First of all, it's imperative
that every last one of
the locusts hear the call.
In order to do that,
we've got to get
our amplifier speaker
at the highest possible point
to get maximum range.
Now, we've got ours
on the roof of this building,
which is one of the tallest
in chicago.
Once we get them here,
I see. Then the boat
will take over.
Exactly. Once we have them
in the heart of the loop,
near our location,
they'll be within range
of the amplifier on the boat.
Now, we'll then radio our
oscillator signal
out to the boat,
and they in turn
will rebroadcast it
over their amplifier,
directing the locusts to them
and into the lake.
We hope.
See, that's what you do so well.
You cut me down.
Will you check and see
about the temperature?
I know a scientist
that needs a back rub.
How can we be sure, sure?
Hm? What do you mean?
How can you know
that we'll get them all?
That's where our observation
posts and the helicopter
come in.
From their reports
we'll know the exact location
of the locusts at all times
and if it's working.
It's 70 degrees, ed.
Cooler near the lake.
They're probably
starting to move.
Emergency lab
to all observation posts.
Emergency lab to all
observation posts, report in.
I'm hiding from a lion.
...to emergency lab, over.
It's got these women
scared stiff.
What is your location?
Over.
I am situated in a store
across from the art institute
on michigan boulevard.
Olga bras are on sale.
Nothing in sight.
Out.
Observation post number three
to emergency lab.
I'm on the roof
of the drayton hotel.
I see
a huge swirly crown roast.
I don't see any grasshoppers
in this area.
But the south side's
getting some action.
- Wow.
- Out.
Emergency lab to observation
post one.
Emergency lab
to observation post one.
You did not report in.
What's your location...
Nothing going on here.
Observation post number one.
I'm right
in the middle of them.
I'M JUST SOUTH OF 73rd
AND SOUTH SHORE DRIVE.
OUT.
And jimmy ferlick's mom says
I can stay for dinner.
Emergency lab to helicopter.
Over.
The name's jeffrey.
I happen to be in a helicopter.
The locusts are active
on the south side of chicago.
As yet there are none
in the downtown area.
Out.
Can you read me,
emergency lab?
Over.
Yes, we can read you fine,
general.
Are you all set?
Over.
We're not quite ready yet.
Dummy here can't fix
the radio.
A few more minutes.
Over.
I think we better start now,
general.
If they should change
their direction
and start moving away
from chicago,
we may not get them all.
Over.
I don't like your starting
until we're completely ready.
This boat has to draw them
away from you
at a split second's notice.
Uh, righty tighty.
Over.
I'd like to start, sir.
- Then go ahead.
- Baby.
I say go, that guy jumps.
I'm going to polygraph my tie.
Yes, sir?
Is that the wire that leads
to the speaker on the roof?
Sure.
Plug it into the amplifier,
will you?
[Imitates electrical buzzing]
[Imitates scream]
[Amplifier whirring]
[Louder whirring]
All right, playing tull
out the window, man. Whoo!
When brian eno ruled chicago.
I don't remember that.
Post number one
to emergency lab,
the locusts are leaving
this section.
They're heading
toward chicago's downtown.
If they wanted to rev up
the grasshoppers,
they just should've played
some marvin gaye.
Helicopter to emergency lab...
I'm still paul frees.
They're moving
on the downtown area.
They are radically altering
their size
depending on your perspective.
So does this bus go
all the way to...
Just get on the bus.
We've got to get organized.
Hoppy.
Observation post number three
to emergency lab.
The locusts are everywhere.
Yep, over there, too.
Everywhere pretty much.
They're moving
towards your location.
I repeat. The locusts are moving
towards the emergency lab.
They've gotten hold
of fire arms and they're drunk.
Michigan boulevard
is filled with them.
They're everywhere!
They're on a shopping rampage!
Emergency lab to boat.
It's working, general.
It's working.
You never take me anywhere.
I heard the reports.
Wow, would you look at that?
They dyed the river green.
That dick daley.
We're in the famous loop now,
harry.
Wonder why they call it that.
[Chuckles]
Wacker.
- Wacker.
I'm blowing the life.
This is bogus.
Yep.
I'm right behind you, okay?
[Laughing]
Oh, man.
Looks good.
Everybody, I think we're okay.
Pretty good shape.
Nothing to worry about.
Intelligence, sophisticated
equipment. I think--
[Screams]
- [Man screaming]
- That's what I said.
You wanna take over
that watch post, honey?
Are you as turned on as I am?
Here they come.
They're coming down the street.
Get the funniest looks
from everyone they meet.
What do you want?
They're climbing the building.
And their feet are dirty.
That's a postcard.
Boy, watch it.
You're stepping
off the building there.
[Mutters]
Wainwright to boat.
Come in, please.
Come in.
Come in, wainwright.
How soon are you ready?
We're ready as soon
as we get clearance
from observation posts.
I'll check them immediately.
Out.
Yeah, as soon as marconi here
is ready.
Boat to helicopter.
They're still going in, sir,
but it'll be a while
before they all reach
the downtown section.
Wainwright,
you'll have to hold out
a bit longer.
All the locusts haven't reached
the downtown area yet.
Excuse me.
I'm on the phone here.
All right, we'll try.
Want some?
Hah!
Not again.
What a day.
Safe yourself, tony!
Top of the wrigley building, ma.
Not quite the top.
We can't hold out much longer.
Look, I wanna talk.
I wanna live.
I wanna--
[Screams]
Watch it, cal.
Boat to observation post.
Well, we're not going to get
this going.
Over.
Post number one,
jimmy's mom serving meatloaf.
Post number two.
All clear, sir.
Helicopter reporting.
This guy's crazy up there.
Oh, the third time.
How stupid am I?
Think about our 10,000 kids?
Hey, I'm just going
to the observation deck.
[Screams]
Bust my chops.
Whenever you're ready, general.
Then let's have it.
Okay, go ahead, audrey.
[Whirring stops]
Throw the switch.
- [Loud whirring]
- Oh, jiminy, shut that off!
Geez, I'm out of here.
I know when I'm not wanted.
Don't shoot.
Good-bye. I'm out of here.
You guys feel
as silly as I do?
Street beef.
Get off the postcard.
They're going to blow
the postcard.
- You've been distant lately.
- Not now.
Let's spit on them.
Helicopter to boat.
General, they're responding.
They're responding.
They're swarming
toward the water.
Don't linger on that shot.
They're going into the water.
It's a trick.
It's gotta be a trick.
There can't be
that many lady grasshoppers
in lake michigan.
Wow, chicago thought
the alewives smelled bad.
Whoo.
Well, let's see
what this baby can do.
Let 'er rip, private.
Hit it!
Head for shore.
We'll, we've just spent
the goofiest week
of our entire lives.
It's going to be tough
for them.
All they ever really shared
were the grasshoppers.
Yeah.
Didn't this guy cause
the whole thing?
He's gotta be doing hard time
in joliet right now.
No, the grasshoppers
ate joliet.
Hey, slow down there, romeo.
Where's your other hand?
♪ Hey, mr. Arnstein,
here I am! ♪
Hey, tom.
Eeeeyeeessss?
Is this the first movie
with grasshoppers?
You know, I think it is.
I can't remember ever seeing
a single grasshopper.
And then today,
nothing but grasshoppers.
Weird.
Now, come on.
There had to have been one
or two grasshoppers.
- Nope.
- No, siree.
That is weird.
You know, maybe we should read
a postcard here.
Okay, we've got this one
here from canton, amy hikaida.
Put that up on still store,
there, cambot.
They say, as members
of the kim cattrall fan club...
- Crow.
- Kim cattrall.
We wondered
if you were going to view
oliver stone's wild palms.
- No. I don't think of it.
- No.
Well, gotta go.
The fathers and friends
are going at it
in the swimming pool--
- wow. Woo-hoo.
- Wuh-ho.
- Yowza.
- That is salty.
The great thing
about these post cards
people send in, though,
they double
as great bert I. Gordon
special effects.
Check this out.
Oh, no!
Grasshoppers are attacking
the beach in aruba.
[Imitating screams]
[Chuckling]
I got one.
I got one here.
The grasshoppers-- aah,
they're attacking the beatles.
[Imitating screams]
[Liverpool accent]
Defend ringo at all costs.
Oh, they're attacking me.
[Laughing]
Oh, look at this.
Oh, grasshoppers--
they don't care.
Now they're going
for the village of spires
in oldenburg, indiana.
Have you no decency?
Oh, no, grasshoppers
have scaled to the very top
of old earl "fatha" hines.
[Imitating screams]
We are witnessing a time
when the beasts have reclaimed
earl "fatha" hines.
- Crow.
- I'm peter graves.
- Crow!
- I'm done.
I'd say.
Back to you.
Oh, maybe we should go
back down there.
Remember what happened
last time.
Back to you, sirs.
Keep your hands up, frank.
Keep your hands up,
frank.
Ah, mike, caught us
in the middle
of our daily routine.
What's that they say
about boxing, frank?
It's the only real sport.
It's the only honest sport.
It's the sport of men.
Absolutely right.
Grab yourself a beer
and grab me one, too,
fellow fighter.
Okay, because we're men.
We are men!
Yes, you've made your point,
frank.
- We're men!
- Yes, frank.
Oh!
You want a piece of me?
Come on, come on.
Huh?
Oh, oh, frank.
Frank, please.
Please, enough.
I have to get the button.
[Chuckling]
All right, men,
into the woods.
This has been a presentation
from comedy central.